dubtrack.fm 2019-04-03

# Dubtrack.FM | Privacy Policy

## Last modified: January 03, 2018.

### Introduction

Dubtrack.FM is a social DJ Website (the "Site" or "Website") where users can share and discover the latest and greatest songs by tuning in to user-generated playlists. The Site and all of its services ("Service") and features ("Feature") is operated by Dubtrack (the "Company", "us" or "we") for the users ("you").

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; in this policy we will explain how we treat your personal information. Since our site is built off content that you provide, including shared information from third party sites, it is important that you keep yourself up-to-date with this information. As we grow, this policy may change to govern changes in the site.

When using the Site, you may find links to other websites, apps, servers or tools that enable you to share information with other websites, apps and services. Dubtrack is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites, apps or servers and we recommend that you review the privacy policies of each of these websites, apps or services before using Dubtrack or sharing any personal details.

Please review this Privacy Policy before you use the Website or any of the services or features offered on or through the Site. By using the Website and its services and features, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you're not permitted to use our Site or services.

### Information We Collect

When you interact with us through the Services, we may collect information from you, as further described below:

**Information You Provide:** We collect information from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you register for access to the Site. Information we collect may include but is not limited to username, email address and any messages, images, links or other content you send via the chat system.

**Data We Collect Automatically:** When you interact with us through the Services, we receive and store certain information such as an IP address, device ID, and your activities within the Services. We may store such information or such information from databases owned and maintained by affiliates or service providers. Third Party Services may use this information and combine it with other information to track, for example, the total visitors to our Site or the number of messages users have sent.

**Information through other Services:** You may give us permission to collect your information in other services. For example, you may sign up to the Site using Twitter or Facebook. When you do this, it allows us to obtain the necessary information to complete your account (For example, your username or your avatar).

**Third Party Services:** We use Third Party service providers who may use cookies or other technologies to collect information about you and your browsing and other usage activities over time.

  * For example, we use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies to help us track how many users are on the Site and to augment your experience when you use our Services. You can find out more information on how Google uses this data here: [https://www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/partners](https://www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/partners/).
  * We also use a Software Development Kit ("SDK") from Bugsnag, Inc. ("Bugsnag"). Bugsnag helps us collect error reports and metadata associated with those errors to help us understand which users are affected by it. You can find out more information on how Bugsnag uses your information here: [http://docs.bugsnag.com/legal/privacy-policy](https://docs.bugsnag.com/legal/privacy-policy/).
  * **Facebook Connect:** You can sign up and log in to our site Facebook Connect. This service will ask for your permission to share certain information from your Facebook account such as your name, username and profile picture to create your account. This information is collected by Facebook and is provided to Dubtrack under their own Privacy Policy: <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>.
  * **Twitter:** You can sign up and log in to our site Twitter. This service will ask for your permission to share certain information from your Twitter account such as your name, username and profile picture to create your account. This information is collected by Twitter and is provided to Dubtrack under their own Privacy Policy: <https://twitter.com/en/privacy>.
  * **SoundCloud:** You can sign up and log in to our site SoundCloud. This service will ask for your permission to share certain information from your SoundCloud account such as your name, username and profile picture to create your account. This information is collected by SoundCloud and is provided to Dubtrack under their own Privacy Policy: <https://soundcloud.com/pages/privacy>. In addition to this, we also use SoundCloud's player embed to allow users to share music from their site. SoundCloud may collect usage data for analytics purposes. You can find out more information on how SoundCloud uses this data here: <https://soundcloud.com/pages/cookies>.
  * **Twitch:** You can sign up and log in to our site Twitch. This service will ask for your permission to share certain information from your Twitch account such as your username and profile picture to create your account. This information is collected by Twitch and is provided to Dubtrack under their own Privacy Policy: <https://www.twitch.tv/p/legal/privacy-policy>.

### Information You Share

When you consult with our customer service team, send us an email or communicate with us in any way, you are choosing to share information with us. That information may include your name, physical address, email address, IP address, phone number, gender, location, or other demographic information. By giving us this information, you consent to this information being collected, used, disclosed and stored by us as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Information We Share

**External Processing**

We use third parties to provide services to us, such as:

  * Managing mailing lists and delivering email
  * Hosting our website
  * Helping us analyse the use of these services

**Legal Disclosure, Safety and Security**

We may preserve, use, or disclose your personal data if we believe it is reasonably necessary to:

  * Comply with a law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request
  * Protect the safety of any person
  * Protect the integrity of our platform, including to help prevent spam or abuse
  * Address fraud, security, or technical issues
  * Protect our rights or property or the rights or property of those who use our services

### Managing Your Data

**Understanding your rights**

It is important that you understand your legal rights around your personal data and how we may use it. If you would like to discuss or exercise any of these rights, please contact our Data Controller at [privacy@dubtrack.fm](mailto:privacy@dubtrack.fm).

  * **Right to be informed:** This Privacy Policy aims to inform you about how we process your personal data. You might also see specific messages when we collect personal data from you that explain why we ask for it.
  * **Right of access:** You have the right to access a copy of your personal data and receive certain information about what the data is and how and why we are processing it. We will ask you to prove your identity before we can disclose any information.
  * **Right to rectification:** You have the right to request a correction to your data if you believe that any information we hold is incorrect.
  * **Right to erasure:** You have the right to request that we delete your data. There are some circumstances where we may need to keep your details, for example, if we are legally obliged to do so. If this is the case, we will explain and discuss these circumstances with you.
  * **Right to restrict processing:** You can request that we restrict processing of your data, as an alternative to deleting it - this means that we will keep the data but stop processing for most purposes. You may want to exercise this right if you feel that the data is inaccurate, that our processing of it is unlawful, whilst we progress a request from you to object to processing, or if we have no further need of the data, but you require us to keep it in relation to the establishment, exercise or defense of a legal claim.
  * **Right to data portability:** You have the right to request a copy of your data, in machine-readable form, and have us transfer it to another organization. There are some circumstances where these rights may not apply, but where this is the case we will always explain this to you.
  * **Right to object:** You have the right to object to the processing of your data.
  * **Rights related to automated decision making:** You have the right to avoid being subject to decisions based solely on automated processing (including profiling) which has a significant effect on you. We do not carry out any such processing.

### Cookies

We use cookies to help us uniquely identify an account and to hold your user session. We use cookies on our main site, beta site and in our API. We also allow you to create an account and login to our site using your credentials on Third Party Sites through their API. These sites may use cookies to track your web browsing and have separate privacy policies that you must read.

We may also use tracking cookies to help ourselves improve the quality of the service we provide.

### Where Your Information Is Processed and Stored

The Company is based in the United States. No matter where you are located, you consent to processing and transferring of your information in and to the U.S. and other countries. The laws of the U.S. and other countries governing data collection and use may not be as comprehensive or protective as the laws of the country where you live.

We may host data with third parties and allow third parties to access, maintain, or otherwise use your information for purposes that we deem conductive to improving our service and company. You also hereby agree that we are not liable for any privacy breaches that may occur because of the actions of third parties. How you interact with our site may be shared with third party services that you used to login, which means you are also storing information on their system, which is governed by their own agreements.

### Children

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, please do not submit any personal information though our Services, access or use the Service in any way. If you become aware of a user who is under the age of thirteen, please contact us and we will deal with the matter accordingly. You may be required to submit satisfactory proof of age in order for you to continue using the Service if your account has been disabled for the reasons above.

### Changes to This Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time for any reason without notice. Please review this policy from time to time, and especially before you provide any information to us. The date of when this policy was last updated can be found above. Your continued use of the Services after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

### Contacting Us

If you have any question regarding this Privacy Policy or the information practices of our Services, please contact us with the following email: [support@dubtrack.fm](mailto:support@dubtrack.fm)
